smokingeverywhere.com 2010-11-28

# Smoking Everywhere E-Cigarette Privacy Policy

Smoking Everywhere, LLC. believes Our Distributors are the heart of the Company, and that they provide you with great advice, product selection and service. You are a valued customer and we strive to give you the support necessary so that your Smoking Everywhere experiences are great ones.

If you have concerns or questions about this statement or about Smoking Everywhere online privacy practices, you should contact Smoking Everywhere Inc. at [support@smokingeverywhere.com](mailto:support@SmokingEverywhere.com).

**Applicable Web Sites**

This online privacy statement applies to Smoking Everywhere, LLC. and covers the U.S. corporate-operated Smoking Everywhere Web sites (www.SmokingEverywhere.com). Smoking Everywhere Distributors may also operate their own Web sites, called Smoking Everywhere Replicate Web Sites. Each distributor is an independent contractor having the right to operate their own Smoking Everywhere business. In this regard, distributor online privacy practices may vary.

**Information Collected and How It Is Used**  
In order to gain use of the site (become a “user”), we require you to disclose the following information:  
Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
Enroller ID

We may use the Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you shall find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, you may “opt-out” of doing so by sending an email to us at [support@smokingeverywhere.com](mailto:support@SmokingEverywhere.com).

If you choose to post information on our site or maintain email, or telephone contact with us, we may retain such information also and its transmission via email is not secured.

**Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties**  
We may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our site. The parties who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant bank, our Internet Service Provider) may also have access to your information in performing such services. Should we buy or sell assets of our company, another company may need to review our company’s assets, including your information, to make business decisions as to whether to acquire such assets. Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law We may be required by subpoena, law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to us.

**Technical & Aggregate Information**  
Smoking Everywhere, LLC. collects certain technical and browsing information from visitors to the corporate-operated Web site including www,smokingeverywhere.com (the "Site"), such as the domain name used, pages visited and the date and time you logged on. Such information helps us make the Site more useful to visitors. Technical and browsing information from visitors also may be combined with the information of other visitors on an aggregated basis. Combined technical and browsing information may be disclosed to third parties to assist in these purposes. Technical and browsing information for individual visitors is not disclosed to third parties.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on your computer's hard drive. When you view the Site, some information in the form of a "cookie" may be automatically stored on your computer. This allows us to tailor the Site to your specific interests and preferences. If you want to disable these cookies, most Internet Browsers will allow you to delete cookies from your computer hard drive, prevent them from being stored or signal a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

Our site’s servers also automatically identify your computer by its Internet Protocol address which is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. Your IP address may be used to address problems with our server or administer our site or to gather broad demographic information about our users. We passively collect your IP Address.

**Security**  
Data security is important to Smoking Everywhere, LLC. and we have industry-leading technology in place to ensure any personal information you voluntarily submit is safe including secure sockets layer (SSL) technology to protect the storage and transfer of your personal information. Visitor information is stored in secured databases and is protected from unauthorized access.

**Children's Online Privacy**  
The Smoking Everywhere Web site is not intended for use by children and we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. You may learn more about protecting children’s privacy online by visiting www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy .

**Notification of Changes**  
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the applicable site. Please check for information about revisions to our online privacy policy. If, however, we are going to use visitors' personal identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify those affected via e-mail (if applicable).

**Consent**  
Smoking Everywhere, LLC. respects the online privacy of all online visitors. By using the Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Smoking Everywhere in a manner consistent with the guidelines stated in this policy.

**Contact Us**  
We use e-mail links on this page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have and try to reply promptly. We use this information to respond to your questions and may record your comments to improve our customer service. If you have any questions about the Smoking Everywhere, LLC. Online Privacy Statement, please e-mail us at [support@smokingeverywhere.com](mailto:support@SmokingEverywhere.com).

**YOUR USE OF OUR SITE MEANS THAT YOU ARE ACCEPT THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THIS POLICY. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO THE POLICY BY POSTING THE NEW VERSION WITH A NEW EFFECTIVE DATE. YOUR CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.**
